["Flower Ring" by
Shino Shimoji, Aya Suzaki plays]
[door squeaking]
[Hiraku groaning]
[Hiraku sighing]
[Lu groaning]
[whimsical music]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
Vampires really don't
like mornings, do they?
But still,
having Lu living here
with me has
helped out in
all sorts of ways.
[bright flute music]
- That should do it.
We should be set
for lights now.
- Wow.
That's so amazing!
- But all I did was basic magic.
This dish really has
a mild flavor to it.
Do you prefer not to use salt
when cooking your meals?
- Nope. I just don't have any.
- Huh?
- There's no salt.
I've been looking for awhile,
but I can't find any.
I'm at the point where
I'm about to...
That's a pretty intense
look on your face!
- Well, of course it is.
Right here.
This is mostly salt.
We can dissolve some,
then boil it.
Did you not notice
while you were digging?
[Hiraku groaning]
That's a pretty intense
look on your face.
[Lu yawning]
Good morning.
- Hey.
- [Lu] What are we doing today?
- Let me see.
I was planning to
check on the fruit trees.
- Okay.
First, I'm going to
get washed up,
and then I'll head over there.
[bright guitar music]
Look at these.
Did you transplant them here?
- Yeah.
They need more time to grow
than the vegetables.
I tried oranges and
peaches this time.
I might try chestnuts next time.
- Oh?
I can't wait to try those
once they're harvested.
[Lu slurping]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
By the way,
the herb tea that Lu
makes is pretty good,
but I wanna drink green tea.
If I remember correctly,
oolong tea and black tea are
all made from processing
the same leaves.
[wood clanking]
[Hiraku gasping]
[Lu gasping]
What is it this time?
[suspenseful music]
[Hiraku panting]
[Lu panting]
[Tia yelling]
- Enough!
Please forgive my behavior!
I understand that I was wrong
for attacking you first!
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I've seen this situation
play out before.
- Help, anyone!
Please rescue me!
Don't let them hurt me!
- Okay!
[Tia sighing]
Are you all right?
- Yes.
I think so.
[Hiraku gasping]
[magical music]
- Wow.
That's amazing.
It's nice to be able
to use magic, huh?
Lu?
- So this is where you
were hiding out, Lulucy!
Stop resisting and come in
quietly or I'll have to...
[Tia yelling]
Help me!
- [Hiraku] Hey, hey, hey!
- [Tia] Jeez.
I can't believe you hid
in this forest
of all places.
- Well, a lot of stuff happened.
- That was an awful
experience back thee.
- [Lu] I know.
They did that to me, too.
- To you as well?
- Yeah. They're pretty ruthless.
Magic doesn't affect them much,
plus they dodge spells.
- [Tia] Fighting them
is a death sentence.
- [Lu] Yeah.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] They seem
to have a shared experience.
- [Tia] By the way,
who is this person?
- I'm Hira.
- Oh, this person is...
Well...
He's my husband.
- Your husband?
You and Lulucy are a couple?
- What? Yeah.
- [Tia] I wasn't expecting that.
- Yeah. I'm Hiraku.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
Her husband?
That's the first time
she's called me that.
- Let me introduce myself.
My name is Tia.
And as you can see,
I'm an angel.
- An angel?
So, that means
you serve God, right?
[Tia tooting trumpet]
- [Lu] It's nothing
that important.
They're just
a race of warriors
that have more muscles
than brains.
[Tia growling]
- [Tia] How rude!
There was a brief
time period when
we were an object of
worship, you know!
- [Hiraku] So why is an angel
like you chasing down Lu?
- There's a bounty on her for
all of the damage she caused
from one of her rampages.
- There's an actual
bounty on your head?
- Well, yeah.
There was an annoying
noble who kept
forcing me to make medicine
and drugs for them.
They were so incessant
with their demands
that I felt the need
to teach them a little-
- There's nothing
little about it!
She spends all
her time researching
strange medicines
and concoctions,
and then as soon as
something bothers her,
[castle exploding]
she starts blowing
everything up.
[Lu cartoon giggling]
That's the problem.
- Stop making it
sound like I've
done that multiple times!
There was just one accident!
- Regardless, the fact remains
you besmirched the honor
of a noble!
Do you have idea...
- [Hiraku Voiceover] They seem
to get along pretty well.
- Well, I do think I may have
gone a little too far with that.
- I'm surprised you're
willing to admit that.
- So anyways,
the reason I ended up here
is because
I was running from Tia.
After all, she is
stronger than I am.
But only by a little bit.
- Wow, Lulucy.
I'm amazed.
You really have changed.
You never used to be
the kind of person
who would freely admit
to having any weaknesses.
- [Lu] Yeah, well,
I felt firsthand just
how weak I really was.
- [Tia] I see.
Fighting that many should
be against the rules.
- Yeah.
Now putting that stuff aside,
do you wanna live here, too?
- What? Live here with you two?
- Yes, with us.
Right?
- I guess.
- I'll show you around
the crop fields and stuff.
I'm sure you'll love it here
as much as I do!
Let's get going, okay?
- Yeah.
- [Lu] Look!
[bright violin music]
These are the crop fields.
We grow lots of vegetables here.
- [Tia] Wow.
- And this is our orchard.
We have a lot of different
kinds of fruit growing.
[Tia gasping]
This is... Zabuton!
[Tia fainting]
Yeah. That's about
what I expected.
- [Hiraku] Maybe she
doesn't like spiders.
- Hey!
[Tia gasping]
We're about to go and
harvest some crops.
Come with us.
It's a whole lot of fun.
- Kay.
Did you plant all this
stuff yourself, Hiraku?
- [Hiraku] Yeah.
- [Lu] I helped a little, too.
- We really needed some
more hands, so thank you.
- What? You expect me to do
farm work around here, too?
- Of course.
Come on!
- Why does an angel like me
have to get their hands dirty?
- Okay then, let's get
started with the cabbage!
There, you see?
Give it a try, just like that.
- Sure.
[Tia growling]
These are heavy cabbages, huh?
- Wanna taste it?
Here.
Well, all I did was tear up
some cabbage leaves
and sprinkle salt.
[Tia gasping]
- [Tia] It's delicious! Really!
- I'm glad.
- Wow, I never knew fresh
vegetables tasted so great.
- Yeah.
And the ones you
actually grow yourself
taste even better.
- I think you're right
about that.
[Tia sighing]
I think that's enough for today.
- Yeah, that's a good amount.
- That was pretty exhausting.
- It's nice to have so much,
but harvesting them all
is hard work.
- Aw man, if only...
- It's delicious!
This red vegetable you call a
strawberry is so sweet and tart.
- It sure is.
- This farming work
is a lot more
fulfilling than I ever
expected it to be.
- [Lu] You had fun today, right?
- Yes!
- Well, then, that settles it!
You're going to live
here with us, right?
- Well, I...
- Right? Come on.
My body won't be able to handle
everything if it's just myself.
- [Tia] Excuse me?
What do you mean by that?
[bright folk music]
- Tia, I have to say,
this farming work really
does suit you well.
- Was that supposed to be
a compliment?
- Of course it was.
- Very well, then.
I guess we'll just have to
leave it at that for now.
More importantly...
Hiraku!
Can we make a lot
more strawberries?
- I really wish that we could,
but even if we
expanded the crop fields,
we couldn't keep up
with all the harvesting.
I think we're operating
at maximum capacity.
[Tia sighing]
- Yeah, we really could use
some more help around the farm.
- [Lu] You can just
work extra hard
to make up the difference.
- [Tia] What about you?
Are you sure you haven't
been slacking off?
[Hiraku chuckling]
- I really don't think she is.
Besides, if we grow
too much of everything,
then it's likely
we won't be able
to finish eating everything
that we harvest.
[puppies whining]
Oh, it's the new puppies.
Their horns are
already coming in.
[Tia trembling]
[puppies whining]
Good boy.
Kuro and Yuki's children
had children of their own.
They've become quite a
large family of dogs.
[Tia trembling]
Before long,
the puppies will leave
and find partners
of their own.
- Does that mean we'll have
even more puppies later?
[Tia yelling]
- Now that you mention it,
that hut isn't going to
be big enough.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] And so,
we decided to build a dog
area next to the orchard.
[Hiraku sighing]
It looks kind of like
a horse stable,
but I'd like to think that
it turned out well.
I still haven't
come up with names
for the next generation after
Kuroone and his siblings.
I want to give them names,
but there's just so many of them
that it's hard to come up
with something for everyone.
On the other hand,
Zabuton's children...
- [Hiraku] What is it?
[Hiraku gasping]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
Are riding the wind
and starting a new journey.
I guess they're all leaving.
I was planning on
turning the orchard
into their new home.
Oh well.
It looks like some of them are
still staying behind with us.
- Hey.
I'm going to step out
for awhile, too.
- [Hiraku] You're also going off
somewhere and leaving us?
- No, I won't be gone
for too long, promise.
Now then.
- I wonder where she's going.
- Well, she'll be back
before you know it.
- You think so?
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
"Farming Life."
- [Lu Voiceover]
"In Another."
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
"World."
A few days later,
Tia came back just like
Lu said she would.
And she brought
a bunch of girls with her.
- So you're elves?
- We're high elves,
but you can call us
elves if you like.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
What's the difference?
- Please introduce
yourselves, everyone!
- I'm Lea.
- I'm Leef.
- I'm Lecott.
- I'm Leezay.
- I'm Leely.
- I'm Leeta.
- I'm Lees.
- [Hiraku] You're all Le.
- Ah, you mean that
our names all have Le?
We have similar names because
we come from the same family.
We came here after Tia suggested
that we all move here.
Please let us all
live here with you!
- Well, um...
- The truth is,
they all share
a very sad and
depressing backstory.
They all used to live
in a village
far up into the north.
But most of their people were
wiped out after they got dragged
into the war of the humans.
Their race was scattered,
and since then,
they've been wandering the land
looking for a place they could
settle down and call home.
[Lea sighing]
- Until now, we've been
traveling through the woods
trying to do what we can to get
by.
And without a place
to settle down,
it will be impossible
to repopulate our race.
We ask that you help us!
- [Elves] Please help us!
- You can count on them
to be excellent workers.
I implore you to
help them as well.
- I think it's a good idea
for you to accept.
I've heard the high elves
are a very talented race.
I imagine you're all still
pretty young, right?
- I'm the oldest one
within our group.
I'm just over 400.
- I'm the youngest one
in the group,
and I'm about 300.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] I can't
tell they're 100 years apart!
- So, what do you think?
- Fine.
Right, Hiraku?
- Well, we have a lot of
different roommates here,
but if you all promise to
get along, then it's fine.
- [Elves] Thank you
for letting us stay!
- By the way, who are the
other roommates staying here?
- This is Zabuton.
[elves fainting]
And these here...
are the dogs.
[elves fainting]
- [Tia] Yeah, that's about
how I expected it to go.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
The number of people living here
went up suddenly,
so we needed a place
for them to stay.
Lea said the seven of them
all wanted to live together,
so we decided to build them
one big house.
First, we started with the ditch
and the wooden fence.
Then, we made them
their own toilet
and garbage disposal area.
- That was an unbreakable tree
that's harder than steel!
- He cut it like nothing!
- [Hiraku Voiceover] When it
comes to construction,
they know more than I do.
And they're all
really handy, too.
I even got to learn a lot about
how to process lumber and
fit the logs together from them.
I just followed their orders.
I focused on digging holes,
and leveling the ground,
and gathering lumber for them.
It took us 10 days, and then...
- It's finally done!
- Yeah!
- That's amazing!
It's so much nicer than
our little hut, isn't it?
- It really is.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] Jealousy.
- [Lu] Is he sulking?
- [Tia] It looks like it.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
But now I've learned it,
their technique.
[Lu gasping]
It might be a good idea to try
rebuilding the little hut
we've been sleeping in.
[elves chattering]
The house is shaped
like a rectangle
that stretches from
east to west.
Just past the entranceway,
there's a large living room that
doubles as a dining room.
It's a place to work
on things together,
or where they can all eat.
Sitting on both
the left and right
sides of the living room
are storage rooms.
The living room is
an open design
that covers the first
and second floors.
The lighting is done
with magic.
And the second floor room sits
on top of the storage rooms.
The second floor is where
their individual rooms are.
I hope that this can
become a home
where they feel safe
and at peace.
[elves laughing]
- It looks like they've all
gotten used to
settling down here.
- Yeah.
The vegetable harvesting
seems to be going great.
- Yeah.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
They're eating raw garlic
they just picked?
That's pretty wild.
- Huh?
You use fire and
you eat meat, too?
- Yeah, of course we do.
- Whenever I think of elves,
I think of a race
that lives in the woods
and is one with nature
and hates fire and stuff.
[Lea laughing]
- [Lea] Where'd you get
that silly idea?
[Lea laughing]
- Am I wrong?
- How is anyone supposed to live
without having the use of fire?
- Like I said, one with nature.
- How exactly?
- Uh, well, you see,
you wake up with the sunrise,
you go to sleep when it sets.
You eat fruit from the trees.
And you love the forest trees.
And you refuse to wear
anything made of metal.
- Excuse me, Hiraku.
Don't misjudge
how harsh nature is.
If you tried living
like that in the forest,
you would surely die
right away.
- I see, then.
- Good.
- [Hiraku Voiceover] They really
are hardcore survivalists.
- By the way, if it's okay,
as thanks for letting us
all live here,
we were planning on doing some
mining and blacksmithing
work for you.
- Huh? You can do that?
- [Lea] We can.
I'd like to start by
building a furnace
that can melt iron.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I always imagined
that dwarves handled
the blacksmithing.
I guess that's
different in this world.
[dwarf snoring]
Following Lea's instruction,
they put together
a smithing work station.
They put charcoal
and iron sand
taken from the river into the
earthen furnace and heat it up.
Then they hammer the
melted iron to process it.
[metal banging]
[Hiraku chuckling]
- This is amazing!
We're advancing!
- Thank you very much.
- You can really do
everything, can't you?
- Well, yeah.
That tends to happen
when you spend
200 years wandering
without a home.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- The only things
we couldn't do...
were settle down
and finally reproduce!
- Well, we already
took care of one of those.
[elves giggling]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
I thought it would be
for the best if I
didn't say anything
about the second thing
she mentioned.
- I'm really happy you guys
all came to live here.
- Me too.
- I'm happy to hear
that you feel
that way about us, Hiraku.
[leaves rustling]
- [Hiraku] Let's stop
here for today.
- Excuse me.
I'm pretty sure
I saw a wheat field
out over there,
is that right?
- Yeah, we have
a wheat field,
but we already processed and
harvested it into
flour to store.
[Hiraku gasping]
- If it's all right with you,
I would like to bake
some bread for everyone.
- Some bread?
Yes, please, go ahead!
Wait, what's that?
- If you use this stuff in here,
it makes the bread rise up
when it bakes.
[thud]
[bright music]
[Leef gasping]
[magical music]
[bread crunching]
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
That freshly baked bread
tasted amazing!
[bright guitar music]
- This is delicious!
- [Tia] It really is!
- We're all very happy to
hear that you enjoy it.
- [Lu] That's an understatement.
- [Hiraku Voiceover]
That jar must've had
a natural yeast to make the
bread rise inside of it.
Now that we can bake bread,
I'd like to expand
the wheat fields.
- I might be late in asking,
but does this land we're on
belong to anyone?
- You mean like
this forest here?
- Yeah.
- I don't think anyone owns
this plot of land or anything,
but I guess it's under the
control of the demon lord.
- The demon lord?
- Yeah.
- That sounds terrifying.
- Is there some sort of problem?
- Well, it's just do you
think the demon lord
is going to have
a problem with me
building all these crop
fields and stuff here?
- [Lu] Is that what
you're worried about?
Did you receive
any kind of support
when you started
building all this?
- [Hiraku] No, not at all.
- Then there's nothing
to worry about.
If you built this place
all on your own,
then the land belongs to you.
- I guess that's how it works.
- That's how it works!
[bright folk music]
- [Lea] Hiraku is really
full of surprises.
- [Lu] He surprised me
a lot at first, too.
- Not only did he tame all those
inferno wolves by himself
without causing any harm,
but he tamed
a demon spider, too!
He's definitely special.
- And all these crops as well.
Is the soil here
really good enough
to grow vegetables like this?
- Who knows.
I never got to asking him.
- I'm pretty sure he has
a very green thumb.
[Lu sighing]
That said, it's surprising
how lacking he is
in knowledge about the world.
- I know what you mean!
He was saying that he thought
elves were a race that
didn't use fire or eat meat,
that we're one with nature.
- Are you serious?
- Not only that,
but he didn't seem to know
what angels were either.
- That goes a few steps
beyond lacking knowledge.
- You're right.
[bright folk music]
- [Hiraku Voiceover] Oh yeah,
I haven't worked on building
the waterway in awhile.
Maybe I'll ask Lea and
the elves to help me out.
There's lots of work
to do tomorrow.
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
[bright folk music]